Guide to the Mary Hallock Foote Papers, 1863-1924 (inclusive), 1868-1916 (bulk) M0115
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence, 1885-1945; Series 2
  - Swift, Betty Foote, Angus, M. Edith-Jenkins, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Literary Manuscripts, Series 3
  - Manuscript, "Eastern Towns and Western Camps" (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript, "On Trust" (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences of a Victorian Gentlewoman," outline (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, introduction, chapters 1-8 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, chapters 9-15 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, parts of chapters 9-15 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, chapters 16-20 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, chapters 21-25 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, chapters 26-30 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Manuscript, Reminiscences, chapters 31-37 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Journal Articles, Series 4
  - The Century (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Scribner's Magazine (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Biographical Materials, Series 5
  - Mary Hallock Foote, biographical materials (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Foote family biographical materials (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Secondary Source Materials, Series 6
  - Bibliography (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Bookbuyer, "Mary Hallock Foote," by Helena de Kay Gilder, Aug. 1894 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Book reviews, The Chosen Valley (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Book reviews, The Desert of the Sown (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Book reviews, In Exile, and other works (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Book reviews, John Bodeivin's Testimony, "The Last Assembly Ball" (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Book reviews, Little Fig Tree Stories (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Book reviews, A Picked Company (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Book reviews, The Prodigal (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Book reviews, A Touch of Sun (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Book reviews, The Valley Road (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Miscellany, Series 7
  - Chicago World's Columbian Exposition Judge's Passes (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Miscellany, Mary Hallock Foote (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Miscellany, Betty Foote Swift, poetry, artwork (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Graphic Materials, Series 8
  - Pencil drawings, single people, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pencil drawings, multiple people, 2 Oct. 1875-[ca. 1880-1889], and n.d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Pencil drawings, watercolors, people (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Pencil drawings, places, 27 Feb. 1876-12 June 1878, and n.d. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Pencil drawings, pastel, place, 31 Oct. 1894 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Pencil drawings, watercolor, places, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Pencil drawings, things, 29 Feb. 1876, and n.d. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pencil drawings, watercolor, things, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Original prints (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Original prints (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Printer's proofs, people (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Printer's proofs, people (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Printer's proofs, people (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Printer's proofs, people (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Printer's proofs, people (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Printer's proofs, places, things (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photomechanical prints (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Photomechanical prints (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Photomechanical prints (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Prints from books, serials (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, people (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Idaho album, "Some bits of Idaho through blue glass,", [ca. 1894-1895] (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, places, [ca. 1894-1904], and n.d. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, memorial marker for George Augustus Foote, [ca. 1908] (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Oversize Items, 1869-1893; Series 9
  - Typescripts of letters, pre-1869 (Box 12)
  - Typescripts of letters, 1876-1878(?) (Box 13)
  - Typescripts of letters, 1885-1888 (Box 14)
  - Typescripts of letters, 1890-1893 (Box 15)
  - U.S. Geological Survey notebook, contains pencil sketches by Mary Halock Foote (Box 16)
  - Photo album 1 (Box 17)
  - Photo album 2 & 3 (Box 18)
  - Oversize photographs (Box 19)
- Negatives, undated; Series 10
  - Negatives (Box 20)